Timna Aversa

Dear Family,

I'm excited with this opportunity to share a little about me and my childcare experience with you.

I have been in Berlin for 3 months. I moved here with the intention of learning German and going to University later on, so I'm most likely staying in the city for more a few years at least. I'm a Italian citizen so no Visa restrictions apply.

I'm currently looking for full time work in childcare, I would ideally wish to work around 30 hours per week, but am open to a minimum of 20 hours per week. Childcare work will fit into my life perfectly since right now my only commitment consists of taking German classes everyday for 3 hours, even though at the moment my classes are from 5pm to 8pm I can change as necessary to other times of the day.

I choose to work in childcare because children are inspiring, with energy and curiosity they are always pushing you out of your comfort zone. They have so much potential, it's a privilege to be part and help them grow, learn and find meaning in the small steps of life. I love children and to have fun with them while they discover the world.

As you can see from my CV my childcare experience was matured in a private childcare setting, where I had the opportunity to experience caring for children from babies as young as 3 months to 4 years old. While I do love this age based on my previous experience I'm very open to care for older children and develop new skills.

While with younger children I have developed skills such as helping babies reach important developmental milestones and help toddlers with drawing, crafts and letter recognition, when dealing with older kids some of my love for reading, and my skills with computer programming, photography and basic musical literacy can become helpful depending on your children's interests. I'm fluent in Portuguese and English, my German still very basic but developing.

When I was young I had a great opportunity to have wonderful examples and I hope to have the opportunity to be an example to the new generation too.

Yours sincerely,

Timna Aversa

Timna Aversa

Birth Date : 10/04/1996 Citizenship : Italian / Brazilian

Address: Berlin, Germany 12349
Phone: +49 1575 5417345
E-mail: timnaaversa@gmail.com

I love to read to children and to enjoy exploring with them. These are just two of the many reasons why I love to work with children and be part of their lives. Since I have worked with children previously I have developed much patience and rapid decision making to help them in moments of need. I'm always



looking for ways to improve. I believe that a great communication with the family can be a very important part of the job so both parts can make sure that the child is receiving the best care possible.

EXPERIENCE

Steve's Auto Sales Dealership - https://www.stevesautoslcutah.com/index.shtml 11 / 2018 - 09 / 2020

- Front desk and secretary.
- Greeted and assisted customers in a professional manner.
- Received payments online, through phone calls and in the store.

Bear Essentials Academy - http://www.bearessentialsacademy.com/

11 / 2017 - 11 / 2018

- Daycare teacher for two years old.
- Trained in all areas in the age group of 6 months to 4 years old.
- Followed a curriculum, created monthly plans.
- Keeping track of feeding and changing time.
- Daily report to parents on their kids day.
- Cleaning and organization of the kids room.
- Helped with basic skills like coloring, counting, recognizing letters.

EDUCATION

Salt Lake Community College - United States

05 / 2017 - 08 / 2020

On track towards Electrical Engineer, incomplete.

CEEP High School - Brazil

01 / 2010 - 01 / 2014

LANGUAGE

Portuguese: Native

English: C2

German: A2 (Taking Classes)

PERSONAL INTEREST

Photography, I took a photography class in college and have kept it as a hobby since. Front end web development. I love reading and spending time learning new things. I often do crafts.